JOI YAN RONG HUANG

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

San José Costa Rica

PHONE

(506) 7277-3018

EMAIL

rhhaiyin@gmail.com

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

05/26/1989 Costa Rica

SKILLS

Fast Learner

Analytical and Problem-Solving skills

Javascript

HTML & CSS

Git & GitHub

WordPress development

Responsive Web Design

Programming paradigms & principles

Online marketing optimization

CSS frameworks

LANGUAGES

Spanish

• • • • •

English

• • • •

French

• • • 0 0

LINKS

<u>Website</u>

PROFILE

I'm a front-end web developer with over 3 years of experience. I get a kick out of problem solving and learning about new technologies. I work on developing custom WordPress sites for small businesses as well as managing their online marketing. My favourite tool is Github.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

E-mail Deployment Specialist, Cheetah Digital

Mar 2017 — Aug 2021

- Builing of e-mail campaigns using HTML and CSS.
- Quality assurance throughout all stages of deployment.
- E-mail design and developement best practices.
- Creating Account documentation and guidelines.
- Training new team members.
- Client facing communication.

Technical Support Specialist, Concentrix

Dec 2013 — Oct 2016

- Customer handling skills. Providing support in english and french speaking customers, Multitasking inbounding and chat support. Interacting with different cultural backgrounds.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, Universidad Estatal a Distancia de Costa Rica

Jan 2019 — Present

Business Administration Diploma, Universidad Estatal a Distancia de Costa Rica

May 2018 — Present

Responsive Web Design, freecodecamp.org

Certificate Credential

Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures, freecodecamp.org

Certificate Credential

REFERENCES

Edline Monge from Cheetah Digital - Campaign Manager

https://tinyurl.com/52yb5s3e | edline.monge@cheetahdigital.com